asiaing.com 2011-12-12

# Privacy Policy - Asiaing.com: Free eBooks, Free Magazines, Free Magazine Subscriptions

March 05 2007   
  
Thank you for visiting [Asiaing.com Website](http://www.asiaing.com/) and reviewing our privacy policy. Our privacy policy is clear: We will collect no personal information about you when you visit our website unless you choose to provide that information to us.

## Cookies

We do not use "persistent" web cookies. Persistent web cookies are defined as web cookies that can track "the activities of users over time and across different web sites.

## Emails and Web Forms

Personally identifying information that you provide by email and/or web forms will be used only for such purposes as are described at the point of collection (for example on a web form), such as to send information or products to you, process your application, or to respond to your questions or comments. If you provide contact information, Asiaing.com may contact you to clarify your comment or question, or to learn about your level of reader satisfaction with our website. We do not sell any personal information to third parties.

## Information Collected and Stored Automatically

If you do nothing during your visit but browse through the web site, read pages, or download information, we will gather and store certain information about your visit automatically. This information does not identify you personally. We automatically collect and store only the following information about your visit:

   1\. The Internet domain (for example, "your company.com" if you use a private Internet access account, or "your university.edu." if you connect from a university) and IP address.     
   2.  The type of browser and operating system used to access our site;  
   3.  The date and time you access our site;  
   4.  The pages you visit and how long you visited each page; and  
   5.  If you linked to Asiaing web site from another web site, the address of that web site. 

We use this information to help us make our site more useful to visitors and to learn about the number of visitors to our site and the types of technology our visitors use. We do not track or record information about individuals and their visits.

## Links to Other Sites

Our policy discloses the privacy practices Asiaing.com ([www.asiaing.com](http://www.asiaing.com/)). But Asiaing provides [links](http://www.asiaing.com/component/option,com_weblinks/Itemid,145/) to other web sites. 

When you leave our web site ([www.asiaing.com](http://www.asiaing.com/)), you will go to sites outside our control. These external sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data, or solicit personal information. The privacy policies and procedures described here for Asiaing.com do not apply to any external links. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of any site linked from ours, especially if you share any personal information.   

Be informed. You are the person best qualified to protect your own privacy.  

Comments 

Write comment

Last Updated ( March 09 2007 )
